Tejas Dilip Deshpande (1) Featured

Automation Developer seeking assignments in Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, RPA Development, C, C++, C#. Net, ASP. Net, SQL Server, XML, Visual Basic, iQuery, Angular JS



Current Designation: RPA Developer - AA Total Experience: 15 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Acronotics Highest Degree: MCM [Computers and Management]

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Mumbai, Pune
Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Automation Developer,Software Developer,Software Development,Application Programming,Program Management,Project Management,Requirement Gathering,System Analysis,RPA Development,C,C++,C# .Net,ASP.

Net, SQL Server, XML, Visual Basic, iQuery, Angular JS

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

3 years experience in RPA development using Automation Anywhere 10.5.x, 11.3.x

3 months experience in RPA training on Automation Anywhere 10.5

11 years of experience in training C, C++, Data Structures, C# .Net, ASP. Net, SQL Server.

2 years of experience in Software Development and Technical Support.

Work Experience

Acronotics as RPA Developer - AA

Oct 2017 to Till Date

Automation Anywhere 10.5.x, 11.3.x

I was part of the team which has automated business processes from IT and Finance domain of client Hitachi Vantara. I developed 3 bots and was part of team of developers for another 1 bot.

Automated one finance process for client named Arconic. Automated, tested and deployed the BOT in production. I was leading the Production Support team for client Hitachi Vantara. I had a team of 4 people reporting to me. My responsibility included

Creating defect tracker in JIRA, whenever an issue was raised by the client or issue was logged into the logger sheet. Conducting scrum calls to get updated from the team with respect to defect fixing and enhancements.

Guiding the team on defect fixing.

Interacting with the client whenever detailed analysis is required on a defect or to understand the functionality of the enhancement requested by the client.

Client engagement on biweekly basis regarding progress on open issues.

I have been handling RPA projects at client Juniper Networks managing end to end stages of BOTs. My responsibilities include production support, development, feasibility analysis.

Processes Automated -:

1. Salesforce Provisioning (Domain: IT)

Applications:

Service Now (Web)

Salesforce (Web)

Oracle Applications (Windows)

Automating the process of providing access to Salesforce application for HitachiVantara employees who raise the request through their Service Now portal. The bot opens each ticket in Service Now, extracts the user information from the ticket and then based on his request and position type, bot will give Salesforce access. Bot will login to salesforce and search the user. The provisioning involves different stages. First, it fills in the information captured from Service Now ticket. Then it gives permissions to the user based on the permission matrix given in excel format. And finally, if the user has requested to be able to forecast, his Oracle id will be created. After hitting these three applications, bot completes the provisioning process by closing the ticket and notifying user about access. If there are any exceptions, bot sends an email to the Service Desk notifying the same.

Commands used: Object Cloning, Excel Automation, Read From CSV, Insert Keystrokes, Email Automation, Send Email, Metabots

2. Salesforce Deprovisioning (Domain : IT)

Applications: Service Now (Web) Salesforce (Web)

Oracle Applications (Windows)

This process involved removing Salesforce access of those employees who have left the organization. This bot hits the same three applications that Salesforce Provisioning did. Opening each ticket in Service Now, extracting user information and searching the user in Salesforce is a common step in both the bots and I have reused those sub bots here. The next step in this bot is to transfer accounts which were handled by this user to his manager, remove permissions of the user and then finally remove user?s account from Oracle if there is one. The bot sends exception emails wherever applicable. Commands used: Object Cloning, Excel Automation, Read From CSV, Insert Keystrokes, Email Automation, Send Email, Metabots

3. Rebate Calculation (Domain: Finance)

Applications: Salesforce (Web)

Oracle Applications (Windows)

Rebate Calculation is process about calculating the rebate that applies to the items by receiving the quotes from the vendor. The automation bot downloads 5 different reports from Oracle first, combines them in one report and filters them based on certain conditions. Next it downloads reports from salesforce for rebates. These two reports are them combined to create a claim. The bot then connects to the rebate mailbox via Outlook and downloads the quotes attached in email. These downloaded quotes are then inspected by the bot to find sales order number and other details like price, quantity and quote numbers. All these details are extracted by bot and assigned to respective sales order numbers in the claim file.

Arich Infotech as Corporate Trainer

Mar 2013 to Sep 2017

.Net Framework 3.5, 4.0 C#.Net ASP.Net MS SQL Server 2008 MySQL C/C++ and DS DBMS UML

Clients: Cognizant

Vinsys IT Services as Corporate Trainer

Apr 2011 to Feb 2013

C C++ Data Structures using C, C++ DBMS .Net Framework 3.5, 4.0 C# .Net ASP .Net SQL Server 2005, 2008

Clients: TechM, Wipro, Cognizant, Accenture, L & T Infotech, SIT, Kokan Express.

Other projects

Developed content in .Net technology for Fulcrum Worldwide, Pune.

Education

UG: B.Com (Costing) from Pune University in 2006

PG: MCM (Computers and Management) from Pune University in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
C, C++, Data Structures, C# .Net			
ASP. NET, sql server			
Service Now, Salesforce			
Oracle Applications (Windows)			
DBMS, UML			
.Net Framework 3.5/4.0			
Visual Studio 2005/2008/2010			
jQuery, AngularJS			
HTML, XML			
SQL Server 2000/2005/2008			
Mysql 6.0			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				
Kannada				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time